+91 62389 05298

shanofficial2000@gmail.com

Kerala, India

LinkedIn

Website

# **Profile**

A community evangelist with Social Networking, Team, Event, and Social Media Management experience with growth oriented mindset is searching for a Community Manager role in a reputable industry to reach out to and impact more people.

# Experience

### **CAMPUS COMMUNITY MANAGER, TINKERHUB FOUNDATION – JUNE 2021 - PRESENT**

- Worked on onboarding new campuses as TinkerHub Campus Community and onboarded 15+ campuses which helped organisation to reach out to 12000+ students across Kerala.
- Managed 60+ Campuses across Kerala and organised different events called Campus Connect, Innovation Catalyst Workshops, with 50+ participants in each events.
- Mentored 100+ students about importance of a Tech Community in Campuses.

### COMMUNITY OUTREACH CO-ORDINATOR, PYGRAMMERS - APRIL 2021 - PRESENT

- Managed Social Media Platforms Instagram and LinkedIn helped community to reach out to 1300+ Social Media users across the web.
- Organised Instagram Live Sessions with 50+ viewers and other Series about Python Programming to reach out to more Beginners in Python Community.

#### FOUNDER, TINKERHUB SIAS – MARCH 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2021

- Founded a Tech Community called TinkerHub SIAS in my Campus without any Tech Learning Culture which impacted 50+ Students who were passionate to learn Tech.
- Mentored 15+ Community members on how to run a community successfully and what is the importance of a tech community in a Non-Engineering College.
- Organised hackathons which helped 15+ students to figure out their interest in Web Development.

## **CO-FOUNDER, TECHSIAS – JULY 2020 - JULY 2021**

- Co-Founded a Community which bridge gap between Academics and Industry
- Organised Tech events impacting 20+ Students of the campus to learn Tech.

## Education

Safi Institute of Advanced Study(Affiliated by University of Calicut), Vazhayur, Kerala, India – Bachelor of Computer Application(2019-2022)

### Skills

- Community Management
- Digital Tools
- Event Organisation

- Social Media Management
- Team Management and Leadership